Guide to the Russell Van Nest Black papers, 1919-1968.
Black, Russell Van Nest papers
- Series I. Correspondence
  - 1936-1939
    - G Prospects, undated (Box 9, Folder 87)
      Garfield, New Jersey. Zoning.
    - H General, 1939 (Box 9, Folder 88)
      Routine Personal Correspondence. Antrim Haldeman; Virginia Howe.
    - International Congress for Geography, 1937 (Box 9, Folder 89)
    - I Investments, 1939 (Box 9, Folder 90)
    - L General, 1936-1937, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      Rochelle, New York. Zoning. Harold Lewis. "Plan Age".
    - Lancaster Township, Pennsylvania, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      Zoning. Louis Sprecher.
    - L Prospects, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      Lawrenceville, New Jersey; Pennsylvania. Zoning. Commonwealth of Pennsylvania.
    - M General, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      Plainfield, New Jersey. Federal Housing Projects. Earl O. Mills.
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1938-1939 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Mount Olive Township, New Jersey, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - N General, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      New York; New Jersey. Maurice Catherwood.
    - New Hope Fish and Game Association Forestry Committee, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - New Jersey League of Municipalities, 1938 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - New Jersey State Planning Board, 1939-1940 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      Conservation; National Resources; Land Subdivisions. Arthur Comey. New York State Planning Board; National Resources Committee.
    - N Prospects, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      New Rochelle, New York; Nutley, New Jersey.
    - National Resources Planning Board, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      New Jersey; Virginia; Pennsylvania. Land Subdivision; Bibliography.
    - O General, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Office (Insurance, etc.), 1938-1939 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Ohio Valley Regional Planning Commission, undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
      Drainage Basin Staff
    - P General, 1938-1940 (Box 10, Folder 16)
      Philadelphia, Pennsylvania. Pennsylvania School of Social Work. Zoning. Planning Education. Institute of Local and State Government; City Charter Committee
    - Personal M.H.B., 1940 (Box 10, Folder 17)
      World War II Peace Movement; Personal Correspondence. Women's International League for Peace and Freedom.
    - Personal M.H.B., 1938-1940 (Box 10, Folder 18)
      World War II Peace Movement; Personal Correspondence. Women's International League for Peace and Freedom; New Jersey League of Women Voters.
    - Princeton Borough, 1938-1939 (Box 10, Folder 19)
      Princeton, New Jersey.
    - P Prospects, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 20)
      New Jersey. Planning Boards. Frederick Bigger.
    - Passaic, New Jersey, 1938-1939 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - R General, 1938-1939 (Box 10, Folder 22)
      Housing. Garden Apartment. Dr Rappaport; Robert Randall.
    - S General, 1938-1939 (Box 10, Folder 23)
      New Rochelle, New York. Zoning. Keith Simpson.
    - Salebury Cooperative, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 24)
      Medical Care.
    - S Prospects, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 25)
      Suffern, New York.
    - State Planning Board (Pennsylvania), 1939 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - T General, 1930, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 27)
      Includes Personal Correspondence. Armand Tibbitts; Frances Tibbitts.
    - Teaneck, New Jersey, 1938-1939 (Box 10, Folder 28)
      Zoning. Scott Campbell
    - T Prospects, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 29)
      Trenton, New Jersey. Zoning.
    - U General, 1938-1940 (Box 10, Folder 30)
      Bradford County. Federal Housing; Zoning. Raymond Unwin. U.S. Department of Agriculture.
    - U.S. Housing Authority, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 31)
      Philadelphia, Pennsylvania; Bethlehem, Pennsylvania; Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania; Scranton, Pennsylvania. Housing. Philadelphia Housing Association; Federal Works Agency.
    - U. S. Housing Authority Expense Account Correspondence, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 32)
      Pennsylvania. Housing.
    - Virginia State Planning Board, 1939-1940 (Box 10, Folder 33)
      National Resources Committee
    - W General, 1938-1939 (Box 10, Folder 34)
      Land Planning - Agricultural Planning - New Jersey. Federal. Pearl Buck. U.S. Department of Agriculture.
    - Morton Wallerstein, Regional Chairman, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 35)
      Virginia; New Jersey; Pennsylvania. Morton Wallerstein.
    - W Prospects, 1930, 1939-1940 (Box 10, Folder 36)
      Westchester, New York; West Deptford, New Jersey. Carl Pforzheimer; Frank Sahl.
    - World's Fair Committee, "Civic Films, Inc.", 1939 (Box 10, Folder 37)
      Re: the Film, "The City". Clarence Stein.
  - 1938-1941
    - Y Prospects, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 38)
      Yardley, Pennsylvania.
    - Aero Service Corporation, 1939-1940 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - American City Planning Institute, 1939-1941 (Box 10, Folder 40)
      City Planning Society. American Institute of Planners. Planning Practice. Alfred Kastner, Choethiel Woodard, "Social Function of the Architect".
    - American City Planning Institute, 1940-1941 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - American Society of Civil Engineers, 1940 (Box 10, Folder 42)
      Engineering Practice.
    - American Society of Landscape Architects, undated (Box 10, Folder 43)
      National Planning - Planning Practice.
    - American Society of Planning Officials, 1940-1941 (Box 10, Folder 44)
      Planning Practice; re: Manual on Zoning by Zmerican Society of Planning Officials.
    - Application for Work, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - A Prospects, 1940-1941 (Box 10, Folder 46)
      Atlanta, Georgia. Planning Practice. American Road Builders Association.
    - B General, 1940-1941 (Box 10, Folder 47)
      Bradford County, Pennsylvania; Bucks County, Pennsylvania; Georgia; George Washington University. Zoning; Planning Practice; Planning Education. Rolf Bauhan; Alan Boyer; Fred Bigger; Alfred Bettman. Planning and Zoning Commission - Bradford County.
    - Bethlehem Housing Project, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 48)
      Bethlehem, Pennsylvania. Housing. Antonin Raymond.
    - Bucks County Association, 1940-1941 (Box 10, Folder 49)
      Includes Printed Material.
    - Bucks County Farm, 1940-1941 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - C General, 1940-1941 (Box 10, Folder 51)
      Highway Planning - National Resources Planning - Conservation. Boston; Washington D.C.. Planning Practice; re: The City. Metal Resources
    - Christmas Trees; Advertising and Correspondence, 1940-1942 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - Cornell University, 1938 (Box 10, Folder 53)
      Planning Education
    - D General, 1940-1941 (Box 10, Folder 54)
      Detroit, Michigan; Delaware Valley; Princeton, New Jersey. Planning Education; Planning Practice. Harold Dodds; City of Detroit.
    - Englewood, New Jersey, 1940 (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - E Prospects, 1940-1941 (Box 10, Folder 56)
      Elizabethtown, Pennsylvania; East Bradford Township, Pennsylvania. Property Development; Planning and Zoning Commissions; Zoning. Jean Foulke; Jim Thompson.
    - F General, 1940-1941 (Box 10, Folder 57)
      Flemington, New Jersey. Housing. Housing Projects Defense.
    - William Flemer, Jr, 1940-1941 (Box 10, Folder 58)
      Landscape Practice. Princeton Nurseries.
    - Franklin Township, New Jersey, 1939-1941 (Box 10, Folder 59)
      Fred Bascom. Township of Franklin.
    - G General, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - H General, 1940-1941 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      Landscape Planning - Hatboro, Pennsylvania; Harrisburg, Pennsylvania; New Hope, Pennsylvania; Harvard. Zoning; Planning Practice; Planning Education; State Planning Boards.
    - I General, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Investments, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      Includes Reports
    - J General, 1940- (Box 11, Folder 4)
      Includes Personal Correspondence. Donald Johansen.
    - K General, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      Includes Personal Correspondence. Robert Kohn
    - L General, 1940-1941 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      Lancaster, Pennsylvania. Zoning. R. Oblender.
    - Lancaster Township, Pennsylvania, 1940-1941 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      Zoning. Lewis Sprecher. Landscape Architecture.
    - Long Branch, New Jersey, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      Long Branch, New Jersey. City Planning Board, City of Long Branch.
    - M General, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      Massachusetts Institute of Technology. Planning Education. Frederick Adams.
    - Madison, New Jersey, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      Zoning. Harold Buttenheim. Zoning Board of Adjustment of Madison, New Jersey.
    - Manheim Township, Pennsylvania, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 11)
      Zoning. E. J. Kessler.
    - Manheim Township, Pennsylvania, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 12)
      Zoning. John Souser.
    - Mount Joy, Pennsylvania, 1940-1941 (Box 11, Folder 13)
      Zoning. Clarence Schook. Contract and Map
    - N General, 1941-1941 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      New Brunswick, New Jersey; Newark, New Jersey. New York. Planning Practice. Arthur Comey. Newark City Planning Project; State of new York.
    - New Jersey League of Municipalities, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - N Prospects, 1940-1941 (Box 11, Folder 16)
      Newark, New Jersey.
    - National Resources Planning Board, 1939-1941 (Box 11, Folder 17)
      Highway Planning - Regional Planning - National Planning - Conservation - New England; Hampton Road; Delaware River Basin. Re: "Long Range Programming of Public Works"; Planning Practice; Water.
    - New Hope Fish and Game Commission, 1939-1941 (Box 11, Folder 18)
      New Hope Fish and Game Association. New Hope Fish, Game and Forestry.
    - P General, 1940-1941 (Box 11, Folder 19)
      Pennsylvania. Defense Housing.
    - Passaic, New Jersey, 1940-1941 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Princeton, Borough, New Jersey, 1939-1941 (Box 11, Folder 21)
      Zoning. Borough of Princeton.
    - Programs and Conference Arrangements, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 22)
      Highway Planning - City Planning Society, American Planning and Civil Association. Legislation. National Conference on Planning. Planning Practice. American Institute of Planners.
    - R General, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - S General, 1940-1941 (Box 11, Folder 24)
      Southhampton, Pennsylvania; New Hope, Pennsylvania. Landscape Development; Policy; Zoning. Clarence Stein; Howard Strong; L. Segoe; John Soucer.
    - S Prospects, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 25)
      Solebury, Pennsylvania. Zoning. Land Development. Stotesbury tract.
    - T Prospects, 1940-1942 (Box 11, Folder 26)
      Towanda, Pennsylvania; Tampa, Florida; University of Southern California. Zoning; Planning Education. Armand Tibbitts. City of Tampa Zoning Commission.
    - U General, 19410-1941 (Box 11, Folder 27)
      University of Pennsylvania. Planning Education. Jane Unwin; Raymond Unwin.
    - W General, 1931, 1940-1941 (Box 11, Folder 28)
      Newcastle, Delaware; Warminister, Pennsylvania; Westchester County, New York. Zoning. Defense. "Planning and Zoning Problems". Westchester County Planning Fedeartion, 1931. Robert Wheelwright; Willis Wissler; Richarson; Blair. Wintersteen and Williams; War Department.
    - Watchung Borough, New Jersey, 1940-1941 (Box 11, Folder 29)
      Zoning. Planning Board.
  - 1935-1941
    - Agenda, Rules, Purpose, Policy of National Resources Board of Pennsylvania, 1937-1938 (Box 11, Folder 30-34)
      National Planning. National Resources Committee.
    - Expense Account Correspondence, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 35)
      National Resources Planning Board.
    - Incodel (Called Delaware Valley Conference in Previous Files), 1938, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 36)
      National Resources Committee; Interstate Commission on the Delaware River Basin
    - National Resources Committee; Local Planning Committee, A-C, 1938-1939 (Box 11, Folder 37-38)
      Land Use; Federal Aid, State and Local; Bibliography, Land Subdivision. Conservation, Soil; re: R. Black, "A New Definition of Local Planning".
    - New Jersey State Planning Board, 1940-1941 (Box 11, Folder 39-42)
      Highway Planning - New Jersey. Defense Preparation. National Resources Planning Board.
    - New York State Planning Board, 1939-1940 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Ohio Valley Regional Planning Commission (See Pennsylvania State Planning Board), 1935-1936 (Box 11, Folder 44)
      Alfred Bettman.
    - Pennsylvania State Planning Board, 1940-1941 (Box 11, Folder 45-46)
      Recreational Planning; New Jersey. Zoning; Metropolitan Region.
    - U. S. Housing Authority, 1940-1941 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      Allegheny County, Pennsylvania; Johnstown, Pennsylvania; Beaver County, Pennsylvania; Montgomery, Pennsylvania; Paterson, New Jersey. Housing. Federal Works Agency; Department of the Interior.
    - Virginia State Planning Board, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      T. Ledyare Blakeman. Commonwealth of Virginia; National Resources Planning Board.
    - Morton Wallerstein, Regional Chairman, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      National Planning - Regional Planning - Region II (New York, New Jersey, Pennsylvania, Virginia). National Resources Planning Board.
    - Morton Wallerstein, Regional Chairman, 1940-1941 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      National Planning - Regional Planning - New York; New Jersey; Pennsylvania; Virginia. National Resources Planning Board.
    - Works Progress Administration, 1936, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      Federal Planning - Public Works; Unemployment. Federal Emergency Administration of Public Works.
    - State Planning Programs, 1937 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      Typed materials.
  - 1940-1942
    - A General, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 7)
      Community Health and Civic Association.
    - Aero Service Corporation, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - American Civic Association, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - American Institute of Planners, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      Planning Practice. Includes Personal Correspondence.
    - American Society of Landscape Architects, 1940-1942 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - American Society of Planning Officials, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Applications for Work, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - B General, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 14)
      Harold Buttenheim; Alfred Bettman
    - B Prospects, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Bridgewater Township, New Jersey, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 16)
      Township Planning - Bridgewater, New Jersey.
    - Bucks Farm, 1941-1942 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Bucks County Farm, 1943 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - C General, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 19)
      Arthur Comey
    - Civic Films, Inc, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 20)
      re: film, "The City". Clarence Stein.
    - C Prospects, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 21)
      Clifton, New Jersey.
    - Chatham Township, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 22)
      Chatham, New Jersey. Zoning. Planning Board of the Township of Chatham.
    - Crawford County, Pennsylvania, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - D General, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 24)
      State Planning - Post War.
    - Davison Place House, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 25)
      Includes Personal Business Correspondence.
    - D Prospects, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Delaware Valley Protective Association, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - E General, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Expense Account Correspondence N.R.P.B., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 29)
      Includes Vouchers.
    - F General, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Federal Housing Administration, 1941-1942 (Box 12, Folder 31)
      Wartime Housing. Earle Draper; Howard Strong; Frederick Bigger.
    - G General, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 32)
      Includes Personal Correspondnce and Matters.
    - G Prospects, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 33)
      Thornbury, Pennsylvania. Zoning.
    - H General, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 34)
      FPHA. B. A. Haldeman
    - H Prospects, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - I Prospects, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Investments, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - J General, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - K General, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 39)
      Kearny, New Jersey.
    - L Prospects, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 40)
      Regional Planning - Lansdale, Pennsylvania; New Jersey. Zoning. Typescript Report.
    - Long Branch, New Jersey, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 41)
      Clippings
    - M General, undated (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Manheim Township, Pennsylvania, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 43)
      Zoning. E.J. Kessler.
    - Mount Joy, Pennsylvania, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 44)
      Zoning. Clarence Schock.
    - N General, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 45)
      Maurice Neufeld; Howard Strong.
    - National Resources Planning Board, 1941-1942 (Box 12, Folder 46)
      Public Planning.
    - New Brunswick, New Jersey, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 47)
      Contract.
    - New Hope Fish and Game, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - New Jersey Municipalities -file, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - New Jersey Planning Board, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - Nutley, New Jersey, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 51)
      Edgar Sergeant. Town of Nutley Planning Board.
    - O General, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - Office (Insurance, etc.), 1942 (Box 12, Folder 53)
    - P General, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 54)
    - P Prospects, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 55)
      Pottstown, Pennsylvania. Zoning.
    - Passaic, New Jersey, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 56)
      City Planning Commission of Passaic.
    - Pennsylvania State Planning Board, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 57)
      F.A. Pitkins.
    - Princeton Borough, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 58)
    - R General, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 59)
      Arthur J. Reed.
    - Regional Office - National Resources Planning Board - Fleisher & Wallerstein, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 60)
    - S General, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 61)
      re: Progressive urban Planning Project. Ladislas Segoe.
    - S Prospects, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 62)
      Somerville, New Jersey. Zoning.
    - T General, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 63)
      Armand Tibbitts
    - U General, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 64)
      Upper Gwyneed, Pennsylvania. Zoning.
    - U.S.H.A. Expense Account Correspondence, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 65)
      Federal Works Agency; Vouchers.
    - V General, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 66)
      State Planning - Virginia.
    - W General, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 67)
      Pennsylvania. Zoning
    - Watchung Borough, New Jersey, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 68)
    - Wilson Borough (Meuser Park), 1942 (Box 12, Folder 69)
      Park Planning - Easton, Pennsylvania.
    - W Prospects, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 70)
    - XY General, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 71)
    - National Association of Real Estate Boards, 1942 (Box 48, Folder 4)
      Includes some other planning notes on redevelopment and cash-grants-in aid.
  - 1939-1945
    - A General, 1943 (Box 12, Folder 72)
      State Planning - Pennsylvania; Bridgewater New Jersey. Zoning; Aerial Photography. Frederick Adams. Executive Office of the President.
    - A General, 1944 (Box 12, Folder 73)
      New Brunswick, Connecticut. R. Black "Maps and Surveys for Planning"; Post-war Automobiles. Correspondence, Paper.
    - Aero Service Corporation, 1943 (Box 12, Folder 74)
      Lebanon, Pennsylvania.
    - Aero Service Corporation, 1944 (Box 12, Folder 75)
    - Allentown, Pennsylvania, 1944 (Box 12, Folder 76)
      City Planning Commission for the City of Allentown.
    - American City Planning Institute, 1924-1943 (Box 12, Folder 77)
      Planning Education; Draft Status; Post-war; re: Application of Michael Burris. Tracy Augur; Michael Burris. American Institute of Planners.
    - American Institute of Planners, 1944 (Box 12, Folder 78)
      R. Black, "The Composite Profession of Planning"; Journal of American Institute of Planners; Planning Education; R. Black, "Factors and Procedures in Determining Need and in Selecting Sites for Low Cost Housing". Papers.
    - American Planning and Civic Association, 1943 (Box 12, Folder 79)
    - American Planning and Civic Association, 1944 (Box 12, Folder 80)
    - American Society of Civil Engineers, 1943 (Box 12, Folder 81)
    - American Society of Civil Engineers, 1943-1944 (Box 12, Folder 82)
    - American Society of Landscape Architects, 1943 (Box 12, Folder 83)
      Planning Practice. Landscape Architecture.
    - American Society of Landscape Architects, 1944 (Box 12, Folder 84)
      Review: R. Black, "TVA - Democracy on the March; R. Black, "National Planning". Gilmore Clark. Landscape Architecture.
    - American Society of Planning Officials, 1943 (Box 12, Folder 85)
      Lancaster, Pennsylvania; Planning Practice.
    - American Society of Planning Officials, 1944 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - B General, 1942-1943 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      Syracuse, New York.
    - B General, 1944 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      Syracuse, New York; New Jersey State Planning Board. Alfred Bettman. The American City.
    - B Prospects, 1943 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      Cincinnati, Ohio. Zoning; Planning Practice. Alfred Bettman.
    - B Prospects, 1944 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      Bridgewater, New Jersey; Broome County, New York. Zoning. Office of Planning and Zoning Board.
    - Bucks County Farm, 1942-1943 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      Routine Personal Business
    - Bucks County Farm, 1944 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - C General, 1942-1943 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      Portland, Maine; Syracuse, New York. Arthur Comey; Jacob Crane.
    - C General, 1944 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      American Society of Landscape Architects. Planning Practice. Re: "The city". Arthur Comey. Civic Films.
    - Chatham Township, New Jersey, 1943 (Box 13, Folder 10)
      Zoning. Planning Board of the Township of Chatham.
    - Christmas Trees, 1944 (Box 13, Folder 11)
      Orders; Business Correspondence.
    - Christmas Trees Advertising and Correspondence, 1943 (Box 13, Folder 12)
      Includes Personal Business.
    - Civic Films, Inc, 1943 (Box 13, Folder 13)
      "The City". Memorandum
    - Committee Reports (American Institute of Planners), 1944 (Box 13, Folder 14)
      Re: "The City". Minutes.
    - Cornell University, 1943 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - C Prospects, 1944 (Box 13, Folder 16)
      Charlotte, North Carolina. Charlotte and Mecklenburg Planning Committee.
    - D General, 1944 (Box 13, Folder 17)
      Allentown, Pennsylvania.
    - D Prospects, 1944 (Box 13, Folder 18)
      Dayton, Ohio. Dayton District Development Committee.
    - E General, 1943 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - E General, 1943 (Box 13, Folder 20)
      Includes Personal Correspondence. Charles Eliot.
    - E Prospects, 1943 (Box 13, Folder 21)
      East Orange, New Jersey. Charles Huitt.
    - E Prospects, 1943-1944 (Box 13, Folder 22)
      Easton, Pennsylvania; East Orange, New Jersey.
    - Expense Account Correspondence N[ational].R[esources].P[lanning].B[oard]., 1942-1943 (Box 13, Folder 23)
      Executive Office of the President.
    - F General, 1944 (Box 13, Folder 24)
      Park Planning - Post-war Planning - Wilson Borough, Pennsylvania.
    - F Prospects, undated (Box 13, Folder 25)
      Flemington, New Jersey. Zoning and Planning.
    - F Prospects, 1944 (Box 13, Folder 26)
      Transportation Planning - Fairlawn, New Jersey. Borough of Fair Lawn.
    - Federal Housing Administration, 1942 (Box 13, Folder 27)
      Temporary Housing. National Housing Agency.
    - William Flemer, Jr, 1943 (Box 13, Folder 28)
      "Experimental Town"
    - Flemington, undated (Box 13, Folder 29)
      Flemington, New Jersey. Contract.
    - Flemington, New Jersey, 1943-1944 (Box 13, Folder 30)
      Borough of Flemington, New Jersey.
    - G General, 1943 (Box 13, Folder 31)
      Presidential Election, 1944.
    - G General, 1943 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - G Prospects, 1944 (Box 13, Folder 33)
      Garden City, New York. Zoning.
    - H General, 1943 (Box 13, Folder 34)
      Includes Personal Correspondence.B. Antrim Haldeman.
    - H General, 1944 (Box 13, Folder 35)
      Allentown, Pennsylvania. Planning Profession. B. Antrim Haldeman.
    - H Prospects, 1943 (Box 13, Folder 36)
      Hamilton Township, New Jersey.
    - H Prospects, 1944 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - I General, 1944 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Interstate Commission on the Delaware River Basin, 1943 (Box 13, Folder 39)
      Regional Planning - Delaware River Basin; Post-war programs. Interstate Commission on the Delaware River Basin.